

BHARATH SRINIVASAN

Administration and Operations Manager

Accomplished and goal driven Executive offering more than 10 years of extensive experience with management and tactical leadership. Offers expertise spanning business administration and change management, achieving optimal results with competent planning and organization and solutions-oriented approach while driving business growth, profitability and strategic alliances. Aim is to successfully lead a team in the organization and to give ample support to the sales team in giving quality output. Diplomatic leader and analytical thinker able to inspire and cultivate productive working relationship with employees and partners.



Bharath19.srinivasan@gmail.com



Bharath.srini



IP Extension, Patparganj, New Delhi - 110092



linkedin.com/in/bharath-srinivasan-92524a24/

AREA OF EXPERTISE

Data Management& QMS MaintenanceRisk ManagementProcess ImprovementInvoice, Ledger ManagementCorporate ManagementBusiness DevelopmentVendor ManagementPlanning and ImplementationCorporate AdministrationQuality ManagementOperational Revenue GenerationOperational Strategies

WORK EXPERIENCE

April 2018 to September 2020

Manager Operations and DMC

- Understand Management and employees for the successful business needs, audit compliance, tracking process towards goal and maintain data.
- Measuring data analytics, revenue, and operational finance system.
- Successfully handled up to 15 groups in a single season with passenger movement of almost 800 people in a season.
- Financial assessment and vendor management.
- Liaising with vendors, partners and clients to make sure quality product is delivered.
- Facilitate the development of operational process and strategic business goals.

January 2016 to February 2017

Manager International Team

- Oversaw a team of 20 executives for International travel packages.
- Provide direction and developed teamwork for optimal revenue target with principles to attain short-term and long-term goals of selling.
- Reviewed daily targets and build team strategies for revenue goals.
- Providing expert solution for travel operation purpose and maintain the quality management services for better output.

Address: 1F, Neethi Apartment, Plot No 84, IP Extension, Patparganj, New Delhi – 110092 Mobile No: 9971374855

EDUCATION

- PGD in Mass Communication
 Sri Sri Centre for Media Studies, Bangalore
 Year 2007 to 2008
- BA in Political Science
 PGDAV College, Delhi University
 Year 2004 to 2007

TECHNICAL SKILLS

AWARDS & RECOGNISTION

- Best supporter and contributor for Sales and Marketing (June 2020)
- Star Performer and Quality Compliance (Q2, FY 19-20)

INTERESTS:

- Wildlife and Nature photography, Old heritage architecture photography
- Teaching, Camping, Trekking, Adventure rides and tours, Travel

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Strong Interpersonal, Team & Customer Service Skills
- Strong Social media skill with knowledge in advertising
- Strong skill in Event & Travel organizing

LANGUAGE

English OOOO Hindi OOOO

Tamil OOOOO Kannada